LeBron LeBron LeBron James
LeBron James
LeBron J-
LeBron LeBron LeBron James
LeBron James
LeBron J-
They don't make em' like him no more
They wanna be around his hoes
They been having his film on gold
They been seeing how great our king was
I don't feel no pressure
Strafing the cage
Just to show the love for the GOAT
I don't need no extras
Search this world ain't no one better
'Cause that, that's
LeBron LeBron LeBron James
That's tough
Who wanna be as great as him?
Who wouldn't wanna be influenced
Take over, four minutes laid by him
Gotta stay focused, can't lose it
'Cause I gotta be in a place like him, I swear
LeBron LeBron LeBron James
LeBron James
LeBron J-
LeBron LeBron LeBron James
LeBron James